Blake Torrey

(425)890-2472 | Btorrey1998@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/blaketorrey/

About Me

Possesses strong problem-solving skills, with four years of experience in analytical chemistry, microbiology, and health care. Seeking further opportunities to expand knowledge of health-related analysis and technology. Motivated, organized, and with a great curiosity to learn.

Experience

LAB TECHNICIAN | MYRIAD GENETICS | JUNE 2023-PRESENT

- Histotechnology training on proper utilization of a microtome to prepare tissue samples for pathology and further analysis.
- · Learned processing procedures for sample handling and testing verification.
- · Applied proper cleaning and sterilization technique to avoid contamination of DNA/RNA samples.

MEDICAL ASSISTANT | BAHR DERMATOLOGY | JUNE 2021-JUNE 2023

- Contributed to accurate and timely documentation of visit notes, including diagnosis, prescriptions, and continuation of care.
- Learned proper sterile technique for phlebotomy, medicine preparation as well as intralesional injections, and providing assistance during surgeries.
- Taught and coached new assistants on nomenclature, documentation, and the responsibilities required of an assistant.

FRONT END ASSISTANT | COSTCO WHOLESALE | AUGUST 2020-JUNE 2021

• Responsible for increasing work efficiency, training new employees on customer service skills, food and beverage preparation, and health and safety standards.

Education

UNIVERSITY OF UTAH; SALT LAKE CITY, UT

MAY 2021

- CHEMISTRY, BS.C
- BIOLOGY, BS.C

Skills & Abilities

- · Safe and Efficient Laboratory Techniques
- · Phlebotomy and medicine preparation
- · Sample Documentation and Processing
- · Experienced in public facing roles
- · Problem solving and communication
- · Trained in Microtomy sample preparation

References:

Brooks Bahr, M.D. – Provider at Bahr Dermatology
Anne Wylie HTL (ASCP) – Supervisor at Myriad Genetics
Sydnie Mordue – Office Manager at Bahr Dermatology
Contact: (385) 321-5837
Contact: (208) 709-8010